<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jane Wang&#39;s private blog</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jane Wang&#39;s private blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Jane Wang</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/post/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Feynman&#39;s words</title>
      <link>/post/feynman-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/feynman-words/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These words come from Feynman&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/proffeynman&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Richard Feynman‏ @ProfFeynman  Oct 27 It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter how beautiful your theory is. If it disagrees with experiment, it&amp;rsquo;s wrong. In that simple statement is the key to science.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Richard Feynman‏ @ProfFeynman  Oct 25 We must be careful not to believe things simply because we want them to be true. No one can fool you as easily as you can fool yourself!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Richard Feynman‏ @ProfFeynman  Oct 26  I was an ordinary person who studied hard. There&amp;rsquo;s no miracle people!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Richard Feynman‏ @ProfFeynman  Oct 30 hours ago Teach principles not formulas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Richard Feynman‏ @ProfFeynman  Oct 30 There is no &amp;ldquo;authority&amp;rdquo; who decides what is a good idea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Richard Feynman‏ @ProfFeynman  Nov 03 Religion is a culture of faith; science is a culture of doubt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Richard Feynman @ProfFeynman Nov 03 Students should be made to think like scientists, be open-minded, curious, and especially, to doubt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Richard Feynman @ProfFeynman 10月31日 Teach principles not formulas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Richard Feynman @ProfFeynman 10月30日 There is no &amp;ldquo;authority&amp;rdquo; who decides what is a good idea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Richard Feynman @ProfFeynman 10月28日 I&amp;rsquo;m smart enough to know that I&amp;rsquo;m dumb.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10月25日 We never are definitely right, we can only be sure we are wrong.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10月23日 Physics isn&amp;rsquo;t the most important thing. Love is.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;11月05日 When we know that we actually live in uncertainty, then we ought to admit it; it is of great value to realize that we do not know answers!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;11月07日 You&amp;rsquo;re unlikely to discover something new without a lot of practice on old stuff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nov 5 The statements of science are not of what is true and what is not true, but statements of what is known with different degrees of certainty.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nov 12 It is imperative in science to doubt; it is absolutely necessary, for progress in science, to have uncertainty as a fundamental part of your inner nature. To make progress in understanding, we must remain modest and allow that we do not know.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nov 10 The only way to deep happiness is to do something you love to the best of your ability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nov 21 If you cannot explain something in simple terms, you don&amp;rsquo;t understand it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nov 23 Teach principles not formulas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Religion is a culture of faith; science is a culture of doubt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is imperative in science to doubt; it is absolutely necessary, for progress in science, to have uncertainty as a fundamental part of your inner nature.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We must be careful not to believe things simply because we want them to be true. No one can fool you as easily as you can fool yourself!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scientists are explorers. Philosophers are tourists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you have any talent, any occupation that delights you, do it, and do it to the hilt. Don&amp;rsquo;t ask why or what difficulties you may get into.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
